Thank you for your invitation, because due to the pandemic and due to work, I was not able to go to the Shanghai conference.
Therefore, I can only share a few things with you in our company in Guangzhou.
Let me introduce myself first.
Our company is called Guangzhou City Satellite Fashion Co., Ltd.
We are engaged in the supply chain of fast fashion brands and fast fashion stores in Europe and the United States.
We have been in this industry for more than 10 years.
I am also a user of Code 3D.
I have been learning about 3D since two years ago.
I have been using it officially for more than a year.
So, I would like to share with you from the perspective of a user,
some of the benefits and values of 3D technology in design development and production.
Thank you.
I would like to share three things with you.
The first thing I would like to share with you is that
in my understanding, digitalization is a trend.
It is the first application in our company.
Actually, the purpose of using 3D is very simple.
I would like to upgrade this industry.
Especially, some changes in the purchasing market can be adapted.
Then, it can improve the competitiveness of our company in a new industrial change.
Because now, the purchasing market has raised a greater demand for us as suppliers.
Moreover, its professional level is getting higher and higher every year.
When we use 3D technology,
or when we use digitalization to upgrade our company,
the main purpose is to adapt to the current requirements of the purchasing market.
In this way, our customers will have a higher annual salary.
We can serve our customers well.
In this way, we can improve our competitiveness in this industry.
So, more than a year ago,
we started to cooperate with Code 3D.
Of course, until now,
the application is just a part of it.
So, I would like to share with you
the application of Code 3D in our company.
Actually, I use it in three aspects.
The first one is that it is used by a relatively small number of people.
I use it in the marketing and e-commerce products of the Internet.
I use it for the display of a product on a platform.
The other two are for the use of 3D technology in OEM and ODM.
So, in these three aspects,
I will talk about it first.
Now, it has a preliminary result.
Because in terms of 3D applications,
there are still many scenes that can be applied.
There are also many functions that can be produced.
So, in the process of implementation,
we also invested a lot of energy
to learn and train more people
who can master this technology,
who can master the use of 3D software together.
So, simply put,
although it took a little more than a year,
it also achieved some results.
Let me briefly introduce it.
For example,
our new product development on Samsung,
because I now do several channels,
OEM, ODM,
now I also have some of my own brand e-commerce channels in promotion.
So,
it is very obvious that
one thing is that
the time spent on the design and development of our new product
has been improved by a relatively large efficiency.
And it can bring us some cost compression.
Of course, it also includes
an improvement in the efficiency of our development.
Although the time spent on this is relatively short,
it can indeed bring us
an improvement in various aspects
with this 3D technology.
So, thank you very much.
Thank you for being able to have this fate with Code 3D.
I will focus on introducing one of the things.
I will give you an example.
Because I now have multiple platforms,
e-commerce platforms,
some of the marketing on the Internet,
I will use 3D virtual design
to do marketing and promotion.
I will talk about the Alibaba platform.
I also listed
some of the products that I have just started to use.
In April,
I started to use 3D virtual design
to do marketing and promotion.
So, I simply pulled some data from April to September.
In fact,
this year,
especially in the context of the epidemic,
as you can see,
in the past six months,
we have been using
3D virtual design to do marketing and promotion.
We have gained several times the growth.
From the peak of April to September,
in September and October,
we have become the leading business
in the Alibaba platform
in the field of customizing women's clothing.
Moreover,
in the whole of our performance,
in fact,
we have achieved
in the whole company,
in addition to
the fact that
before May,
our Chinese supply chain system has not yet recovered.
Then,
in May and June,
after the recovery,
in fact,
our sales performance
has also gained
nearly twice as much growth.
So,
a digital upgrade
brings us
a more realistic
and immediately visible effect.
So,
we can say that
we have achieved
a more realistic
and immediately visible effect.
However,
very few people
will use
virtual 3D
in Internet marketing
or on e-commerce platforms.
Perhaps,
some more
businessmen
or users
will only use it
in some
actual
development
and so on.
So,
in this regard,
I would like to
use me
to make a case
to use it
in the sales
and
in the
display of
e-commerce products.
In fact,
the effect it brings
is
our normal
and traditional
operation.
It has
more traffic,
more clicks
and even
transforms
into our orders.
I may have
talked about
this 3D
code 3D
software
in our company
before.
But,
in fact,
we are
the first
company
to use
virtual 3D
in Internet marketing
and e-commerce platforms.
In fact,
we are
a
European
and American
brand,
a fast-tracking
supply chain.
We are more involved
in the
design
and development
of clothing.
We are also
a
supplier
of
large goods
from
the
design
to
the
production
to
the
delivery
of
large goods.
We are a
company
that provides
applications
for
the entire
supply chain.
So,
I will
briefly
share
my
understanding
of
the
design
and development
in
OEM.
In the past,
when a customer
gave us a design
or a
picture,
we had to
find
the
matching
of the
fabric
to the
sample
of the
material.
Normally,
it takes
10 days.
But,
now,
we can
communicate
with the
customer
in two days
because
when we
find the
sample
of the
in 3D,
the customer
can see
whether
it is
the
result
he wants.
Secondly,
if we
show
the sample
to the
customer,
we can
share
it online
to the
customer
wherever
they are.
Our customers
are from
Europe,
America,
and China.
In the past,
we made
a sample
and
sent it
to them
in a
express way.
After that,
we sent
them back
and forth
to pay
not only
the cost
but also
two or
three
revisions
to match
the real
needs of
the customer.
Now,
we can
communicate
online
with
the customer.
Normally,
we get
great benefits
from
this.
The most obvious
benefit is
the cost
compression.
The cost
compression
is
the international
shipping
fee.
I have
lowered
the fee
by
100,000
to 200,000
per month.
Then,
through
the
need
of
two or
three revisions,
the cost
has been
greatly
reduced.
I think
the cost
of 50%
is still
low.
If the
cost is
high,
we can
increase
the cost
even more.
This is
especially
for
international
trade.
As a
cross-border
supply chain
company,
3D
can
really
achieve
high-efficiency
coordination
at any time
and break
time and
space.
This
is
an
unimaginable
situation
in the
past.
So,
I would like
to say
that
digital
transformation
can really
help us
to increase
efficiency.
We
as a
development
and production
company,
we have
a high
demand
for
our
customers.
We
have
to
offer
customers
the
most
suitable
models
for
their
development.
We
also
offer
more
ODM
models
for
customers
to
design
For a month, we may have to develop 100 or 200 of these physical samples for the client,
and then send them to him or ask him to come and select them.
But now, I can select them in advance for a very long period of time,
for example, one or two months.
I will use a 3D method to select some physical samples for our clients.
After he or she has selected them,
we will make some changes based on the client's opinion,
and then we will go online to communicate.
We will only make a physical sample with no problem.
In this way, my development cost will be greatly reduced.
More importantly, the productivity rate of my physical sample
will be increased.
I will be able to use it for a very long period of time.
For example, in the picture below,
we have 27 hours of practice.
Of course, we may not be able to do it now.
But now, I can do a 2-day practice.
For the productivity rate,
it is more than 55%.
Now, it has increased by about 2-3 times.
So, in terms of development,
in terms of design,
in terms of the connection of the sample,
it is indeed a benefit for us,
those who are working in this field,
to be able to bring real benefits.
Then, I will take a look at the 3D technology
in terms of our production.
It is a very shallow understanding.
In terms of this,
actually, I am using it now,
because we also have our PLM system,
and we also have some of our other production systems in ERP.
So, in terms of CODE 3D,
it can directly display a sample after we modify it.
Then, it also does a division of the process.
As we often say,
it is a function of automatic bumping.
Then, in terms of,
if it is like the traditional way we used to do it before,
it is,
it's that,
the flow,
we call this,
clothing from development to production,
the whole flow process,
in fact,
its efficiency is very low.
It depends on people,
it depends on directly printing the sample,
and then,
to send it to our workshop,
such a situation.
Now,
because if I,
I use 3D to directly,
I was at that time,
the part I just talked about,
it may be the part of communication with customers.
In fact,
in the board room,
in terms of communication with our production workshop,
in fact,
3D can also bring the same effect.
We directly put some of the samples produced,
some of the samples produced,
and pass them on to our production workshop,
and apply them directly to production.
So,
so,
for this,
for our whole chain,
it is an upgrade of the production,
3D,
I think it is a very important middle ring.
And now,
for me,
if it was before,
for example,
because the style we made,
the one we made,
including a fabric database,
including our paper database,
in fact,
in a traditional self-made enterprise,
it did not get a very good second use,
or even a third use.
If we use this 3D now,
in fact,
in the early stages of development,
we have already divided these digitalized,
some,
including,
let's say,
the attribute of the fabric,
including some of the scan of the fabric,
to make a division,
including the style,
we talk about the platform,
including the paper,
the paper,
including the sample of paper,
to make a division share,
and then,
in our database,
it does in fact,
for productionいつ,
often,
we do need go back and find,
from our database,
can get an immediate or effective,
in fact,
it will reduce the cost of our many second-time development.
In addition,
in the process of production,
to modernize it,
a greater efficiency.
So,
More importantly, it can accumulate the data-based wealth of our company.
Because in the past, such wealth may be forgotten in half a year or thrown away.
So this is also the overall value of 3D in our production.
Since I have limited time, I will simply share my understanding.
In my understanding, I will use a paragraph to explain my own understanding.
In fact, the upgrade and transformation of 3D is a necessary path.
I have only used a part of it.
Of course, I haven't gone to the next step yet.
This is a very mature stage.
But it can be said that in the production chain,
its communication and writing efficiency has really improved a lot.
Therefore, it is a very intuitive and efficient transformation that we can really feel now.
And in terms of using virtual reality to replace physical reality,
I think it is very good.
Thank you.
Yes, thank you very much.
Well, part of it, I think it's three-sided.
It has a very obvious improvement in our efficiency and cost.
First, I think it is enough to handle our clients
The quality of the paint, or the result after the dyeing has already reached the best dyeing result in this 3D, in fact, I have compared many places.
It can accurately show the effect of the physical dyeing.
At least it is close to the maximum, maybe more than 90%, 80% or 90% of such a density.
In this regard, in fact, even the physical dyeing can not get such an effect.
Because the result is different.
Photography with a 2D screen and a 3D display are still different.
And then,
the communication between us and the brand and some e-commerce users,
including the pattern of the board, the pattern of the pattern, such a modification,
in fact, this effect is really timely.
And it is a very fast response speed.
Because of the online modification,
after the online modification,
we only went to produce the physical dyeing.
In fact,
this is a very fast process.
It can really compress a lot of costs.
And then,
the last point is,
it may be a simple understanding,
because I am a partner of some European and American local brands.
So for some cross-region, cross-country,
for an enterprise like us,
I just talked about it.
Maybe to a large extent,
I just calculated it.
Maybe 200,000, 300,000, 100,000, 200,000,
a monthly cost compression,
and a time compression.
So the 3D customer can really bring,
although the time I use is not too long,
but for me,
the development,
the communication with customers,
the marketing,
and the production,
the improvement it brings to me,
it is very timely.
And the effect it can produce,
it is very obvious.
Of course,
I hope to get more familiar with it later on.
With the continuous upgrade of Cross 3D,
it can be applied better at the production end.
It will have more of a role at the production end.
Thank you, everyone.
Because I have limited time today,
I will share it with you.
Thank you.
Michael,
don't leave the connection first.
Everyone,
Michael, don't leave our connection first.
If anyone has any questions for Michael,
please raise your hands to Michael for questions.
Sure.
Okay.
Hello, I have a question.
You talked about
You have recommended some brands to customers.
How did you decide to use this 3D software?
I can't hear you very clearly.
Can you hear me clearly?
Yes, you can.
I want to ask, have you recommended any brands to your customers?
Can you hear me?
Yes, you can.
And then, about the recommended style, I want to ask,
how did you decide to use this 3D software to recommend?
How did you resolve from 2D, which is physical clothing, to 3D?
Hello, hello.
Can you hear me clearly?
How did you resolve from 2D, which is physical clothing, to 3D?
I can't hear you very clearly.
Can you hear me clearly?
Well, I want to ask,
If you could please be more clear.
Yes, that's very clear.
So, I want to ask,
when you recommended a new style to your customers,
did you use this 3D software to recommend?
What is your recommendation when you switch from physical clothing to 3D fashion?
How do you solve the problem of changing the clothing from food to a picture?
There are two ways to solve this problem.
The first way is to make a 3D virtual suit for the customer.
We will show the product to the customer from the call set.
We also created a cloud platform.
It is called SaaS.
It allows customers to cooperate with us more effectively.
They can go up there and put our pictures and virtual suits on the cloud platform.
Customers can see them in person.
After they make a choice,
of course, many customers need to modify some things.
The next day, we will make a change on the 3D software.
Then we will ask the business team to go with them.
This is the second and third time to make a change.
For example, some customers may not use 3D software.
Do they have any problems when you recommend the picture at the beginning?
Yes, they do.
How do you solve this problem?
First of all, their sense of adaptability.
In fact, in the process of promotion,
for many of our customers,
it is normal for them to understand that they are not used to it.
But I am also a constant customer to convince them.
I think this can help the customer.
It also helps our supply chain to improve efficiency.
Then, for the second one,
we will start to try it.
Because the technology of Closed 3D after rendering is relatively mature.
If we make a sample from 3D,
it can really be close to the physical sample.
It's like a physical sample of 8 or 9 layers.
But for the second one,
it's a little bit different from the real physical sample.
Including the texture,
including the fabric you are looking for,
it's still a little bit different.
So, how about we show it to him from the picture of the fabric?
Or in fact,
if he is really not at ease,
we will send him a physical sample.
But after all,
it's enough to send it once.
For example,
I don't need to send him 100 samples.
If he has any problems,
I will send it to him.
That's it.
Thank you.
Then, I have another question.
You mentioned that after using 3D software,
you recommend the production rate of the sample.
Is this major improvement
reflected in the fact that you can modify it in time
or that you can recommend more samples in a short time
to increase your production rate?
It's the first one.
The first one is
because we have more designs,
maybe some design drafts,
some pictures,
plus a part of 3D.
After all,
3D development still needs some time to do.
In terms of quantity,
of course,
the fastest is that we may have collected a lot of design drafts,
pictures,
and so on.
What I mean by an increase in production rate
refers to the number of samples
of the physical sample.
Moreover,
because we used to
make a sample
in a real way
in order for him to choose.
Now,
I will give you an example.
If the picture is not OK,
I will pass it.
Or if it is 3D,
and he needs to change it,
I will change it immediately.
If he thinks that
this is what he wants,
then we will make the physical sample.
So,
I think
it's a good idea
to change it.
So,
the first thing I want to talk about
is the rate of use of the physical sample.
It will be higher.
OK.
Thank you.
Can I cut it like this?
Yes, you can.
Thank you.
OK.
Do you have any other questions?
If not,
we would like to thank
Michael for his speech today.
Thank you, Michael.
Thank you.